September 28th, Stellar Year 2148
I'm scared! It hurts so much!
No! Help me!
I guess we're dealing
with every single Legion in the area.
Shin!
Shin, that voice...!
Keep going.
If you can hide in the forest,
they won't be able to find you easily.
Wait for them to pass and then move on.
Wait!
Raiden, you're in charge.
What about you?
I'll catch up after I defeat them.
We can't move on until they're gone.
I don't want to, anyway.
And...
I guess he doesn't want
to let me get away.
If you'd just ask me to fight with you...
Hell no. I'm not following that order.
I'll hold off the rest of them.
So do this quick!
You're a fool.
So are you!
Don't die.
I found you, brother.
Something's weird!
They're trying to pull us away from Shin!
This isn't how Legion fight.
It's that Shepherd's orders.
He wants some private family time.
Anything I shoot won't get through.
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
He wants to kill me with his own hands.
Is that it?
I'm the same, brother.
Reloading! Back me up!
Again? How much ammo are we using?
I'm not counting!
Don't worry.
If we can just lower their numbers
a bit more...
It seems that
they're not interested in retreat.
Fine by me.
Let's do this!
Lieutenant Shuga,
I'm borrowing your left eye!
Here they are.
Prepare for impact!
Is that you, Major Milizé?
Yes. It's me.
All personnel, I'm sorry I'm late.
Are you an absolute moron?
Trying to share visual perception...
I simply confirmed the impact.
Oh, I'm sure sharing visual information
is distracting,
so I'll close my left eye.
Don't you know Handlers don't do that
because it causes blindness?
And those are the mortars!
You didn't get permission!
So what?
Blindness doesn't set in immediately.
Breaking orders and using the guns
without permission won't kill me!
The Republic doesn't play by any sane rules.
So there's no reason for me to, either.
I should've done this a long time ago.
You're a real idiot.
I'm not doing it for you.
If this many Legion break through the front lines,
the Republic is in danger.
I'm just fighting
because I don't want to die.
I'll handle the reinforcements.
Handle the enemies you're fighting
on your own.
Fine, leave it to us.
This is nothing new for us.
Where's Captain Nouzen?
Fighting his brother?
That's what he's after.
He can't hear our voices now.
Enemy withdrawing!
Yes!
We did it.
Captain Nouzen!
Captain Nouzen! Come in!
Shin?
Wake up, you fool!
What is that?
Damn it! We've got to stop it!
But how!
Lieutenant Kukumila, determine the enemy's position
as accurately as possible and send it to me.
I'll let you do the final guidance.
Just hit it with the targeting waves.
Do you mean—
Are you going to hit it with artillery?
It's too close! You'll hit Shin!
I have a plan.
I don't want to let him die, either.
I held back a lot,
and it was still so fragile.
I may have hurt you,
but I'll apologize for that,
and everything else, later.
Finally... Finally you're coming back to me.
We can be together again.
I'll read you a book again.
But first,
I'll get rid of your human body!
Little insects...
You're wasting your time!
Explosive Projectile
You pieces of shit...
You're going to let Shin die, too?
Shin...
I'll protect Shin!
You want to protect him, but...
That's right!
I have to protect him!
He's my brother! I love him!
You want to protect him,
but you're going to kill him again?
I...
The rounds are duds?
All rounds landed on target.
But that won't even slow him down.
We have to do something, now!
Captain Nouzen's signal is back online!
Shin! Wake up, you fool!
Stop messing around!
Get up already!
Shin, are you okay?
Shin...
That Mom and Dad died.
The fact that I'm about to die.
It's all your fault,
Shin!
My brother hasn't forgiven me.
He still blames me.
So...
That's why you're going
to give him his rest, right?
Shin!
I...
I wanted you to...
Goodbye, brother.
I get it now.
You don't need me to hold your hand.
I'm sorry.
Brother?
Shin.
Shin!
Shin...
September 28th, Stellar Year 2148
Major, cut the connection.
He wouldn't want anyone hearing that.
You're right.
It's over.
I told you never to let me
see you again, Lena.
Yeah, I heard you, Annette.
But I never said I wouldn't.
I need to get
into the mortar control system.
As well as the ability to synch vision.
You'll do it to help Spearhead, right?
Of course not.
It's not my problem.
You will.
No matter what it takes.
The boy you abandoned...
His name was Shin, right?
How do you know that name?
There weren't a lot of Eighty-Six
in District 1.
Especially not our age,
with brothers who are much older.
I know your friend well.
I talk to him all the time.
You don't mean...
That's right. He's in my unit.
Combat commander of the Spearhead Squadron.
Personal name: Undertaker.
That's Shin.
Did he tell you?!
Is he alive?
Is he...
Does he still hate me?
What do you care? It's not your problem.
It's not my problem?
It's not...
If that's not the case,
then you need to help me.
What's your answer?
You abandoned him twice.
Are you going to do it a third time?
You're the devil.
That's right, Officer Penrose.
I am, and so are you.
Shin's safe.
Thanks to you.
It's not me who saved him.
He can talk now.
Major...
I thought I heard a voice.
You were there, huh?
Of course I am!
I'm Spearhead's Handler.
Right, right.
You sure are.
The battle is over.
Good work, Undertaker, and all of you.
Thank you, Handler One.
What the hell happened to you, though?
You suddenly turned a bad girl.
"A bad girl"? I didn't...
I just—
I thought you were trying
to blow us up along with the Legion.
Of course not!
She's joking, obviously.
You're so serious.
But don't you think
that's a point in her favor?
That's right. We're grateful, you know.
You saved our lives.
You're all teasing me.
Thank you.
I was finally able to let my brother rest.
That's why you're going
to give him his rest, right?
Shin!
No, it was just a coincidence
that it worked out.
I see.
I can't believe you fired rounds
with deactivated fuses to delay them.
Pretty clever.
Half the rounds were duds,
so I got the idea...
I see.
I'll do even better next time!
Glad to hear it.
I'll set my expectations low.
Now then...
Yeah.
Fido, you got the containers piled up again?
We'll decide on a place to sleep first,
and then worry about repairs.
It's not good that we used so much ammo
on the first day.
I don't think it's a problem.
We certainly took out enough of them.
Sure did.
Let's get to work, then.
Talk to you later, Major.
Hope you can do this
with the next ones, too.
Hey, is it safe to go forward?
A lot of those dud rounds landed.
So it's basically a minefield...
It might not be a good idea
just to go forward.
Shin, can you find us another route?
This is Legion territory,
but there aren't any Legion around here.
We can take any route we want,
but... dud rounds?
We'll tell you as we go.
Shin, you really didn't see anything, did you?
Wait... Wait!
Don't leave me!
Yeah, I like that.
We're not being chased.
We're going on our own,
as far as we can go.
What do you want for dinner?
It's our first day,
so we should do something special, right?
Yeah, but...
I don't know if I've got it in me
to go hunting.
It's rather just go to sleep.
I'm tired.
Wait!
Okay, our goal for tomorrow
is that building.
We've got time. Want to place a bet?
Yeah, how about for
who does the cooking tomorrow?
I don't mind betting,
but I won't hear any complaints
if Kurena or I end up doing it.
Hey!
Fine. You guys suck at cooking,
so that's off the table.
Huh? Do you see something?
Like a building?
You're right!
Is that a cathedral?
A train station, probably.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
if it's a castle or a mansion?
Especially if we can spend the night there.
I've only ever seen castles from afar
on the other side of the combat districts.
I've never been in one.
Let's hunt for treasure!
Yeah.
We're not in a hurry or anything.
It's beautiful.
Pure red all over.
What kind of flower is this?
Is it okay to step on these?
It feels wrong.
Just walking by them
makes the petals fall off.
They were close to falling off
on their own.
All the falling petals are pretty,
but kind of sad.
Seeing the same color of flowers all around and
under you while you fight is actually kind of scary.
The minute we became free,
we got to see something wonderful, huh?
We're right up against the limits
of the Republic's control area.
Just at the barrier of District 86.
Yeah.
We finally made it here.
We've finally arrived.
Outside District 86,
the battlefield where we lived.
Major...
We're going on ahead, Major.
"Thank you."